live welcome brothers and sisters to
another Wednesday question and answer
will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God had written for
the whole world to keep brother James
yes sir and God spake all these words
saying I am the Lord thy God which have
brought thee out of the land of Egypt
out of the house of bondage Thou shalt
have no other gods before me Thou shalt
not make unto thee any Graven image or
any likeness of anything that is in
heaven above or that is in the earth
beneath or that is in the water under
the Earth Thou shalt not bow down
thyself to them nor serve them for I the
Lord thy God am a jealous God visiting
the iniquity of the fathers upon the
children unto the third and fourth
generation of them that hate me and
showing Mercy unto thousands of them
that love me and keep my command
Commandments Thou shalt not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain for the
Lord will not hold him Guiltless that
taketh his name in vain remember the
Sabbath day to keep it holy six days
shalt thou labor and do all thy work but
the seventh day is the Sabbath of the
Lord thy God in it Thou shalt not do any
work thou nor thy son nor thy daughter
thy man's servant nor thy maid servant
servant nor thy cattle nor thy stranger
that is within thy gates for in six days
the Lord made Heaven and Earth the seed
and all that in them is and rested the
seventh day wherefore the Lord blessed
the Sabbath day and hollowed it honor
thy father and thy mother that thy days
may be long upon the land which the Lord
thy God giveth thee Thou shalt not kill
Thou shalt not commit adultery Thou
shalt not steal
Thou shalt not bear false witness
against thy neighbor Thou shalt not
covet thy neighbor's house Thou shalt
not covet thy neighbor's wife nor as
man's servant nor as maid servant nor as
Ox nor as ass nor anything that is thy
neighbors I read Exodus 20:
1-17 may the Lord add a blessing to the
reading of this word in Jesus name we
pray amen amen
so here on question and answer you can
ask us a question and we'll answer it
according to the King James Bible and if
we cannot find the answer we will seek
further counsel to bring you an answer
at a later time keep in mind that all
long scripture questions and all
questions of debate will not be answered
on this program we are here to spread
the true Gospel of God so please be as
direct as possible with your questions
so we can be as direct as possible
with answers out of the King James Bible
nor the Bibles or books will be
acknowledged on this
program and keep in mind this is a live
stream so feel free to send in your
questions that pertain to everlasting
life we just ask that you keep your
scriptures to a two
scripture maximum let me introduce you
the family that's on the panel this
evening we got brother Dre good evening
brother
Jerome gra in peace brother
Julius brother James good evening
everyone sister Deborah good evening
brother Sean good evening and we have
the guest caller with us and I'm brother
Cornell sister debah what is our first
question of the evening um yes there are
several questions that will be answered
first before getting into tonight's Q&A
uh Trisha Israel of God asked in Ezekiel
8 verse1
17 please explain at the end of verse
what is meant by they put the branch to
their
nose they put the branch to their nose
brother
Julius let's go and read that brother
James I'm
there Ezekiel 8 and I apologize good
evening everybody Ezekiel 8 and read
that verse
17 it says then he said unto me has thou
seen this oh son of man is it a light
thing to the house of Judah that they
commit the Abominations which they
commit here for they have filled the
land with violence and have returned to
provoke me to anger and lo they put the
branch to their
nose this is
uh uh the Lord is is rebuking Israel for
their uh mischievous Behavior this is a
type of body language So when you say
you put the breath to your nose it's
body language it's just like somebody
that puts up the middle finger to you
it's just like somebody that put the
hand that means uh talk to the hand let
me show you uh another indication let me
see let's go to Zechariah the 7th
chapter Zechariah chapter 7 body
language so what it represents is direct
disrespect and disregard of God and his
word that's what it mean they put the
branch to their nose but look look at
let's look at another
example Zechariah 7 brother James read
verse
11 it says but they refused to hearken
and pulled away the
shoulder like you you pull away you pull
away the shoulder I ain't trying to hear
hear you go ahead and stop their ears
that they should not hear that they
should not hear so that's what that mean
you pull away the shoulder you stop your
ears so you can hear body language you
put the hand out there say talk to the
hand you put the middle finger out there
when you giving somebody H H you know
that's body language so put the breath
to their nose is body language a total
disrespect of God and his word that's
all I got
right thank you for that brother as we
move on to our next question next
question me to for you Jones
asked the Samaran woman at the whale
with Jesus was she in
Israelite all right this woman at the
whale with Jesus was she an Israelite
brother
Jerome no she wasn't an Israelite uh she
was uh one of the uh Str
that the Assyrians had put in the in the
land after they had taken the nine
tribes out of
Samaria uh let's go take a look at it uh
2 Kings chapter 17 and pick it up at the
22 second Kings chapter
17 read 22-
24 okay 22 through 24 says for the
children of isra Israel walked in all
the sins of jeroboam which he did they
departed not from them until the Lord
removed Israel out of his sight and as
he had said by all his servants and
Prophets so was Israel carried away out
out of their own land to Assyria until
this day and the king of Assyria brought
men from Babylon and from Kath and from
Eva and from ham and from
staia and plac them in the cities of
Samaria instead of the children of
Israel and they possess Samaria and
dwelt in the cities thereof yeah so she
was uh among these people who are
hamites and the Babylon that's ancient
Babylon uh before the Gentiles took it
over so they were hites too that's all I
got all right hope that answer today
question as we move on to our next
next one ran 64 says when We Gather in
the wilderness if we are still alive
during that time and make it will we
make the first
resurrection all right the Wilderness
and will you make the first resurrection
what you say brother Dre let's go to
Ezekiel the 20th chapter Ezekiel 20 and
we gonna pick it up at verse 35 Ezekiel
20 and
35 go ahead brother James when you get
it and I will bring you into the
Wilderness of the people and there will
I plead with you face to
face like as I pleaded with your fathers
in the wilderness of the land of Egypt
so will I plead with you sayeth the Lord
God and I will cause you to pass under
the rod and I will bring you into the
bond of the Covenant
go ahead and I will Purge out from among
you the rebels and them that transgress
against me I will bring them forth out
of the country where they sourn and they
shall not enter into the land of Israel
and ye shall know that I am the Lord so
if you not a rebel you may enter in but
if you are Rebel the Lord is gonna Purge
you
out I hope that answers your question
yes sir want no Purge you all right hope
that answers your question as we move on
to our next next one most love asked in
numbers 36 verse 6 does this law still
stand or does it not matter since we
really don't know what tribe we come
from all right whether or not a law
stands in numbers 36 and 6 let's go
there brother James when you get there
the guest caller will answer it from
there okay numers 36 and6 says this is
the thing which the Lord doeth command
concerning the daughters of zead saying
let them marry to whom they think best
only to the family of the tribe of their
fathers shall they
marry so the person that asked the
question it already it don't matter cuz
we don't know what tribe we're out of
you can't enforce a law and you can't
even decide you can't even determine
what tribe you're out of
so it can't be uh used as
long for that
reason all I have to say all
right as we move on to our next question
hope that answers your question yes JoJo
asked
is remarriage after divorce considered
adultery so after divorce and you get
married again is that considered
adultery gu
call let's see what's written in the
book let's go to Deuteronomy the 24th
chapter read verses 1-
4 okay Deuteronomy
24 veres
1-4 says
when a man had taken a wife and married
her and it come to pass that she find no
favor in his eyes because he has found
some uncleanness in her then let him
write a write her a bill of divorcement
and give it in give it in her hand and
send her out of his house and when she
is departed out of his house she may go
and be another man's wife and if the
latter husband hate her and write her a
bill of divorcement and giveth it in her
hand and sendeth her out of his house or
if the latter husband die which took her
to be his wife his former husband which
sent her away may not take her again to
be his wife after that she is defiled
for this is abomination before the Lord
and thou shalt not cause the land to sin
which the Lord thy God giveth thee for
an
inheritance now Moses wrote that I'm
sure Moses didn't write that without
permission or either
commandment so now let's go into uh
Matthew the 19th Chapter read verses
[Music]
3-9 Matthew
19 verses 3-9 says
the Pharisees also came unto him
tempting him and saying unto him is it
lawful for a man to put away his wife
for every cause and he answered and said
unto them have ye not read that he which
made them at the beginning made them
male and female and said for this cause
shall a man leave father and mother and
shall cleave to his wife and they TW
twain shall be one flesh
wherefore they are no more Twain but one
flesh what therefore God had joined
together let no man put
aunder they say unto him why did Moses
then command to give a writing of
divorcement and to put her away he said
unto them Moses because of the hardness
of your hearts suffered you to put away
your wives but from the beginning it was
not so and I say unto you whosoever
shall put away his wife except it be for
fornication and shall marry another
committeth adultery and whosoever Marth
her which is put away doeth commit
adultery now let's go one other
place let's go into First Corinthians
7th chapter read verses 10-
okay First Corinth thians
7 1 Corinthians 7: 10-15
says and unto the married I command yet
not I but the Lord let not the wife
depart from her husband but and if she
depart let her remain unmarried or be
reconciled to her husband and let not
the husband put away his wife but to the
rest speak I not the Lord if any brother
hath a wife that believeth not and she
be pleased to dwell with him let him not
put her away and the woman which hath an
husband that believeth not and if he be
pleased to dwell with her let her not
leave him for the unbelieving husband is
Sanctified by the wife and the
unbelieving wife is Sanctified by the
husband else were your children unclean
but now are they holy but if the
unbelieving depart let them depart a
brother or a sister is not under bondage
in such cases but God had called us to
Peace So now I've read you three
scriptures written in the
Bible so you know everything I know so
you make your choice that's all I have
to
say all right hope that answers your
question as we move on to our next one
our next one uh Kisha M have two
questions what is the difference between
the body and the soul in Matthew 10
verse 28 and also does God talk or
prophesies to Israelites that don't keep
the Commandments
all right look like we got some body
soul and prophesying what you say
brother Dre let's go to that Matthew 10
and 28 we're gonna read that first and
deal with that and then we'll go to the
second question go read that verse when
you get it and fear not them which kill
the body but are not able to kill the
soul but rather fear him which is able
to destroy both soul and Body in
Hell notice that he's talking about
after death he's talking about hell now
let's look at another account of the
same thing let's go to Luke the 12th
chapter Luke 12 and we're gonna read
verses four and
five pay attention to this Luke 12 4 and
five is going to he is going to give you
a warning here
go ahead and I say unto you my friends
be not afraid of them that kill the body
and after that have no more that they
can do so after a person after a person
kills that body ain't nothing else that
person can do he's telling you to be
afraid of this one he's forewarning you
to be afraid of this one here verse five
go ahead but I will forewarn you whom ye
shall fear fear Him which after he hath
killed have power to cast into hell yay
I say unto you fear Him Now that is the
first death and the second death now
let's go to Revelation the 20th chapter
and look at that Revelation
20 and I want you to read verses
14 no I want you to read read verse 11
start at 11
okay and I S and I saw a great white
throne and him that sat on it from whose
face the earth and the heaven fled away
and there was found no peace for them no
place for them more no place for them go
ahead and I saw the dead small and great
stand before God and the books were open
and another book was open which is The
Book of Life and the dead were judged
out of those things which were written
in the books according to their works
this is the one you should fear this is
the one that after you die and you raise
up this is the one that you got to fear
go ahead and the Sea gave up the dead
which were in it and death and Hell
delivered up the dead which were in them
and they were judged every man according
to their works and it is God that's
gonna judge but go ahead and death and
hell were cast into the Lake of Fire
this is the second death so this is the
one that you got to fear that after he
have killed can raise you up and kill
you again in the second death read verse
15 and whosoever was not found written
in the Book of Life was cast into the
Lake of Fire that is it that's who you
should fear that's the four warning
right there now the second question is
what sister uh yes before that so there
is no difference between the body and
the Soul correct Dre uh brother Dre that
is right the only body the body that you
got is B grain and it's going to raise
up to Eternity and it's gonna be in a
place where God will judge and the
second is the Lake of
Fire that's after he kill the body and
and he can do more he can put you in
that second death man right
so that's why that's what I want you to
understand about that go ahead
yeah so the body and the Soul are the
same and the second question is uh they
ask does God talk or prophesies to
Israelites that don't keep the
Commandments let's go to Ezekiel the 2
chapter Ezekiel 2 we just got a couple
of verses there Ezekiel and we going to
read verses three and four
go ahead brother and he said unto me son
of man I send thee to the children of
Israel to a rebellious nation that hath
rebelled against me they and their
fathers have transgressed against me
even un this
day for for they are imputing children
and stiff hearted I do send them unto
them I do send thee unto them and thou
shalt say unto them thus sayeth the Lord
God so the Lord SS as prophets and they
prophesy so yes is the answer to your
question that's all I got brother
K I'd like to throw a couple things in
there if you don't mind yes
sir I'm go to Genesis the 2
chapter and read verse 7 let's see what
God did with this man
Genesis
2:7 says and the Lord God formed man of
the Dust of the ground and breathed into
his nostrils the breath of life and Man
became a living
Soul okay let's go into First
Corinthians 15th
chapter and we going
uh see what Paul said man was
let's see 1 Corinthians 15
and verse
[Music]
five okay 1 Corinthians 15 verse 45 says
and so it is so it is written the first
man Adam was made a living Soul the last
Adam was made a quickening spirit
tell you the Lord's breath into form Man
Out of the Dust of the ground breathe
into his Lobster the breath of life and
Man became a living soul and then right
here tell you that the first man Adam
was made a living Soul so the body is
the soul I just want to throw that in
yes
sir thank
you you muted
Cornell all right thank you for that
hope that answer question as we move on
to our next our next one Paula e Israel
ask from Matthew 24 vers 16- 28 where is
the place of safety
today all right let's go to Matthew 24
pick it up at that verse 16 where's the
place of safety today and the guest
caller will take it from
there okay Matthew 24-16 says then let
them which be in Judea flee into the
mountains let him which is on the
housetop not come down to take anything
out of his house neither let him which
is in the field return back to take his
clothes and woe unto them that are with
child and to them that give suck in
those days but pray ye that your flight
be not in the winter neither on the
Sabbath day for then shall be Great
Tribulation such as was not since the
beginning of the world to this time no
nor ever shall be and except those days
be shortened there should not there
should no flesh be saved but for the
elect's sake those days shall be
shortened then if any man should shall
say unto you Lo here is Christ or there
believe it not
for there shall arise false christs and
false prophets and shall show great
signs and wonders in so much that if it
were possible they shall
deceive the very elect behold
I the question asked is where is the
Wilderness isn't that
correct yes where's the place of safety
today place of safety same place it was
in the days of Moses
let's go to Exodus the 3
chapter read verse
one Exodus 3 verse1 says now Moses kept
the flock of Jethro his father-in-law
the priest of Midian and he led the
flock to the backside of the desert and
came to the Mountain of God even to
harah so so this is this is huram which
is also another name for siai so that
was in the wilderness right there and so
it's going to be in the same place
because it tell you in Ezekiel the 20th
chapter he going to bring you into the
Wilderness of the people now he going to
plead with you face to face same
Wilderness which at that time was called
in Moses day it was called the land of
Midian nowadays it is
Southwest Saudi Arabia
Southwest of s Saudi Arabia east of the
Red
Sea all I have to say all right we hope
that ansed your question there as we
move on to our next question yes uh
Harold Ferguson says I just found out
that Nike was named after a pagan Greek
goddess is it a sin to wear Nike
no it's not a sin to wear Nike you'd be
surprised a lot of the stuff that we buy
is named after another God but let's go
to that uh first
John go to that First John 3 and let's
read verse
four because you want to know if it's to
wear Nike go ahead brother First John 3
and4 says whosoever committeth sin
transgresseth also the law for sin is
the transgression of the law so no it's
not sin for you to to wear Nike just
because you found out it was named after
a pagan Greek goddess because the word
Nike was named after yeah Greek goddess
of
Victory so that's where the name Nike
came from I mean Air Jordan his shoes
are Nike so all the people that choose
to wear Jordans that's on them you go
into some of the other shoes and wears
of uh rebop that was named after African
antelope so by the time we got through
with the stuff that's named after
something else we found out we wouldn't
be able to wear a lot of stuff Converse
that was named after Maris Mills his
last name was converse that's where the
shoes came from so no it's not a sin for
you to wear the Nike wear and brother
Julius what's the other part of that
also uh we have to remember and if we do
the research you'll find out that the
days of the year and the months are
named after the Roman gods and
planets Sunday is named after the Sun
that shines Monday is named after the
moon and so on you know so on uh your
Wednesday named after Odin and so on
thurs Nam after the Thor all of
it yeah we're not worshiping we just
living this Society but we're not
worshiping
anything right so you want to wear your
Nike gear you okay long as there's no
worship involved and that's all we got
on that thank you for that add on there
brother as we continue to move on with
the time CH yes moving on the time is
801 Valencia says can you tell me why
the people lay their clothes down as s's
feet all right why the people lay their
clothes down at Saul's feet Saul's feet
just happen to be
there but let's go into that acts 8 acts
8 because Stephan here the one that they
ston to death he was talking that word
of God and it was cutting them every
which way Bel loose and they hated on
him for that let's pick it up at acts 8
51 then do some skipping go
ahead acts 8
and
51 there is no 51 in Acts
8 I'm sorry act
seven okay acts 7:51 says ye stiff neck
and uncircumcised in heart and ears ye
do always resist the Holy Ghost as your
fathers did so do ye to this day go go
ahead which of the prophets have not
your fathers persecuted and they have
slain them which showed before of the
coming of the just one of whom ye or
among of whom ye have been now the
betrayers and
murderers who have received the law by
the disposition of angels and have not
kept
it go ahead when they heard heard these
things they were cut to the heart and
they nashed on him with their teeth they
was very upset with him now now they
going out on the death Mission against
him go ahead but he being full of the
Holy Ghost looked up steadfastly into
heaven and saw the glory of God and
Jesus standing on the right hand of God
and said behold I see the heavens open
and the son of man standing on the right
hand of God then they CED then they
cried out with a loud voice and stopped
their ears and ran upon him with one
Accord when he got through talking all
that good word there and they put their
fingers in their ears they didn't want
to hear no more and they cast him out of
the city and stoned him skip down and
read verse uh 58 go ahead and cast him
out of the city and stoned him and the
witnesses laid down their clothes at a
young man's feet whose name was Saul so
the people that was going out to to do
the stoning they just hey took off they
coats and they closed and just laid them
right there at Saul's feet his feet just
so happened to have been there so it's
nothing um else that we can really get
out of that that's all I
got we hope that answers your question
as we move on to our next one moving on
Victor L says can you explain the
parable of the two sons in Matthew
21:
28-32 Matthew
2128 through 32 the parable of the two
sons brother Jerome what you
got let's go read
it Matthews 21:
28-32 but what ye think a certain man
had two sons and he came to the first
and said Son go work today in my
Vineyard he answered and said I will not
but afterward he repented and went and
he came to the second and said likewise
and he answered and said I go sir and
went not whether of them Twain did the
will of his father they said un they say
unto him the first Jesus saith unto them
verily I say unto you that the publicans
and the harlots go into the kingdom of
God before you for John came unto you in
the way of righteousness and ye believed
him not but the publicans and the
harlots believed him and ye when ye had
seen it repented not afterward that ye
might believe
him so uh
it's a parable and when you when you
read about the publicans and the
harlots they represent the first
son that repented and did what the Lord
say about you know the work in in in the
vineyard okay uh but the chief priest uh
and the uh Elders I think you read about
them in the 23rd verse that's who the
Lord was talking to they represent the
second son so the first son at first
said oh you know no we not going but
then they changed their mind in other
words they repented and that's what the
Lord was saying about the harlots and
the publicans yeah they they said No at
first maybe and that's why they was
doing things like being harot but then
when they learned and heard the truth
they they
turn and did what thus said the Lord so
they represent the first son but the uh
Chief priest and the elders that the
Lord was talking to they said yeah we
going we G to do what you say Lord we
going to work in but then they really
didn't do it so they didn't do what the
Lord say and so that they represent the
second
son that's all I got on
it
something yes
sir that's public in the H these are
people nowadays that are just regular
people but the uh uh but the second son
actually
represent the people in the
churches to
Matthew Matthew CH 7th
chapter that's start reading at verse
21 okay Matthew 7 verse 21 says not
everyone I'm sorry sir 21
okay not everyone that saith unto me
Lord Lord shall enter into the kingdom
of heaven but he that doeth the will of
My Father which is in heaven many will
say to me in that day Lord Lord have we
not prophesied in thy name and in thy
name have cast out devils and in thy
name done many wond wondrous works
and they will about now this is talking
about church people only to talk like
this is that
correct not the street P but look what
the Lord's going to say go ahead and
then will I profess profess unto them I
never knew you depart from me ye that
work in
iniquity so these
people going to church every Sunday and
told me how much they love the Lord but
will not keep his
Commandments they keep all these Pagan
days but you get a person in the streets
he the word the first time he believe it
just like they did in John the Baptist
day so the first son
represent the church the second CH
represent anybody that when they hear
the truth they repent and walk in it and
keep God's statue that's all I have to
say
all right thank you for that add-on hope
that answered your question as we move
on to our next question next question
Jennifer uh love says I am so confused
on what we can or cannot do on the feast
days is watching TV considered a
pleasure also is whatever your heart
desires mean food or
drinks all right brother Julius help out
on some of that confusion all
right uh is is watching TV considered a
pleasure it depends on what you're
watching there's a there's a a WiFi
going on
in
California I'm concerned about my
daughter's well-being I got to watch the
news to find out what's going on I need
to watch the news to find out what uh
and and the to watch to find out things
that's going on in the world so it
depends on you can't do anything for
your pleasure but things that are
necessity what if we have to evacuate in
Chicago so you have to watch things
these type of things that's going on in
the world but let me show you what the
Lord said we want you to read Leviticus
the 23rd on your own the 23rd which uh
entails all the feasts of the Lord which
are which are directed toward salvation
but here's one day that you don't do
nothing one day that you don't do
nothing uh of your especially of your
pleasure Leviticus
23 and brother James read verse 26 to
28 okay and the Lord spake unto Moses
saying also on the 10th day of this
seventh month there shall be a day of
atonement it shall be an holy
convocation unto you and ye shall a
flict your souls and offer an offering
made by fire unto the Lord so we don't
do that no more Jesus took care of that
for us go ahead and ye shall do no work
in that same day for it is a day of
atonement to make an atonement for you
before the Lord so I read that to show
you that all of the feast the Lord tell
you what and what you cannot do on all
of the Feast of the Lord certain days
you don't do Sur our work and then on
this day you don't do no work so you
read the whole chapter and then on your
own you go to the Israel of God uh
website and you could uh pull up the
lesson the Feast of the Lord and all
these things are detailed now pertaining
to the second question um uh uh
whatsoever your heart desires mean food
or drinks let's go to
Deuteronomy let's go to Deuteronomy the
14th chapter and let's look at what uh
this pertains
to Deuteronomy
14 brother James and please pick it up
at verse 22 and 23 and then we'll skip
Deuteronomy
14 and begin reading at verse
22 Thou shalt truly tithe all the
increase of thy seed that the field
bringeth forth year by year and thou
shalt eat before the Lord thy God God in
the place which he shall choose to place
his name there the tithe of thy corn of
thy wine and of thine oil and the
firstlings of thy herds and of th of thy
flocks that thou mayest learn to fear
the lord thy God always give me verse 25
25 and
26 then shalt thou turn it into money
and bind up the money in thine hand and
shall go unto the place which the Lord
thy God shall choose and thou shalt
bestow that money for whatsoever thy
Soul lusteth after for oxen or for sheep
or for wine or for strong drink or for
whatsoever thy soul desireth and thou
shalt eat there before the Lord thy God
and thou shalt Rejoice thou and thine
household so this particular uh question
based upon what I'm understanding and
what's written is pertaining to the
Feast of the
Lord whatever your soul desire that's
talking about the food yes that's
talking about food and drinks and that
is pertaining to the Feast of the Lord
no unclean uh drinks of of foods are to
be entertained on the Feast of the Lord
that's the best I can do if anybody want
to
add yeah I want to throw something in
too many people too many people confuse
the Feast of the Lord with the uh uh
weekly Sabbath day when he said don't do
no pleasure anything preach to the Lord
is a time for pleasure and rejoice you
know that's within within reason but if
you go and you read they will tell you
what to do and then some of them said
thou sht do no Sur our work yeah and
only mean don't go to your job it didn't
say nothing else
all I have to say exactly thank you all
right hope that answers your question as
we move on to our
next next question D law says still
sustaining My Life by keeping God's
biblical KJV laws I desire a tight Enoch
like
relationship a friendship to walk with
god without disrespect or fear
advice
please all right that's good you keeping
the laws guest
caller CH I let somebody else give you
some advice go to Matthew the 19th
Chapter read verses 16 and
17 Matthew 19 ver 16 and 17 says and
behold one came and said unto him good
Master what good thing shall shall I do
that I may have eternal life and he said
unto him why callest thou me good there
is none good but one that is God but if
thou will enter into life keep the
Commandments that's all you have to do
that's couldn't
dve Enoch kep it and he got to uh uh uh
he got to get eternal
life Same Love
will get you eternal life just like
Enoch got it that's all I have to say y
like many others in the Bible who's
going to receive the eternal life all
right hope that answered your question
as we move on to our next one uh next
one just know have two questions did
Judas die by taking his own life in
Matthew 27
verse5 or by Falling and bursting open
in Acts 1 verse
18 and was the FI named for the
Pharisees purchased in Matthew 27 verse
6-8 or Judas acts 1 verse
18-9 all right same scriptures just a
couple of questions there brother Julius
let's go to Matthew 27 you answer the
question Matthew 27 and verse 5 Matthew
let's start at verse three brother James
Matthew 27 and verse three okay then
Judas which had betrayed him when he saw
that he was condemned repented himself
and brought again the 30 pieces of
silver to the chief priests and Elders
saying now now skip down to verse
and read it and he cast down the pieces
of silver in the temple and departed and
went and hanged himself now it don't say
right here what he uh uh burst right
here but he killed himself he killed
himself but let's hold this right here
let's go to acts one okay we coming
right back to Matthew 27 okay acts 1 and
let's read that
verse uh 18 and 19 acts 1:18 and 19 when
you get it brother James let's go ahead
and read it now this man purchased a
field with the reward of
iniquity didn't Judas did not purchase
the field because he was dead but his
money that the Pharisees took from uh
that they paid him with he tried to give
it back they took the money and gave it
so his money bought the field of blood
go ahead and falling headl long he burst
aunder in the midst and all his boughs
gushed out so now that had to be
afterwards he had hung himself that had
to be after he had hung himself so now
let's go
back let's go back to Matthew 27 and get
the rest of it
okay now pick up at verse six and
continue and the chief priest took the
silver pieces and said it is not lawful
for to put them into the treasury
because it is the price of blood uhhuh
and they took counsel and brought with
them and bought with them The Potter's
field to bury strangers in so Matthew
act say this man but it wasn't Judas it
was Judas is money but the Pharisees
them they took the money and bought the
field
and uh call the field to bury strangers
in to bury criminals in to bury uh and
what
whatsoever go ahead and
read wherefore the field was called the
field of blood until this day so it
wasn't named after the Pharisees the
Pharisees called it the field of blood
but the original name of it was the pphi
or aoda which means um uh uh the pphi
that's aloda means the field of blood
but the original name was the part of
field where the people would go down and
get their clay dead clay and make their
Ceramics and pottery
with so Judas killed himself by hang he
hung himself afterwards the book said
that his bows gushed out that's the best
I can do with that
all right obvious obvious that the Rope
broke
yep okay yes sir all right thank you for
that as we move on to our next question
next question Eve Davy asks if a woman
should have her head covered when
praying or be sh in 1 Corinthians 11: 5
and six and Thessalonians but they don't
give first or second 5 verse
17 we should always be praying when
should a woman have her head uncovered
and what is her hair purpose also what
is considered praying personal
conversation with the Lord or praying in
a congregation
all right brother Dre we need some light
on that question it's about three or
four questions in there but we gonna
take a stab at it let's go to uh 1
Corinthians
and uh pick it up at verse
two
okay now I pray you Brethren that ye
remember me in all things and keep the
ordinances as I delivered them to you I
read verse five and six go ahead but
every woman that prayeth or prophesieth
with her head uncovered dishonor her
head for that is it for that is even all
one as if she were
shaven for if the woman for if the woman
be not covered let her also be shorn but
if it be a shame for a woman to be shorn
or shaven let her be covered
so normally it's a shame for a woman to
be shamed and then they got things that
they do when they uncover a woman's head
but here what we talking about is every
woman praying or prophesying she should
have her head covered or she is
dishonoring her head verse three verse
three tells you but I would have you
know that the head of every man is
Christ and the head of the woman is the
man and the head of Christ is God but
her husband is her head and she
dishonors her head if she has her head
uncovered if she don't have a husband
she's dishonoring her God now you you
ask questions
about
uh we should always pray you you
got um first Thessalonians 5 because
there is no second Thessalonians 5 let's
go to First Thessalonians 5 and read
verse
17 1 Thessalonians 5 verse1 17 says pray
without ceasing yeah pray without
ceasing so here what we talking about is
that we ought to always pray but if you
going to pray you you asked the question
you said we should always pray when
should a
woman have her head uncovered she should
have her head uncovered when she's not
praying or prophesying but if she
praying or prophesying her head should
be covered or she's dishonoring her
head and you ask the question what is
her hair's purpose well in in uh verse
15 Read verse 15 in 1
Corinthians go back there real quick
verse 15 1 Corinthians 11 1 Corinthians
15 and 11
says
says therefore whether it were I or they
so we preach and so ye believe James 1
First
Corinthians 11 and verse I'm sorry 11
and 15 not 15 and 11 sorry about that 11
and 15
says but if a woman have long hair it is
a glory to her for her hair is given her
for a covering her hair is a glory to
her but her hair is not a covering to
her glory people glorify
hair in fact the hair industry
is16 billion doll
industry yeah spend big money on hair
and they glorifying the hair so the
glory that she has is it's a vain Glory
if you would say but it is not a
covering otherwise a man would have to
be baldheaded because his head is to be
uncovered so we not about hair being a
covering it's a simple thing it's an
ordinance the Lord say the the word say
if you going to come it look cover your
head sister when you praying or
prophesying if you not praying or
prophesying dealing with that you don't
have to but when you come to the Israel
of
God sisters cover their head Brothers
uncover their
head I hope that
helped yes sir and the question where uh
Eve Davey as what is considered
praying is it personal conversation with
the Lord or praying in a
congregation
both it's
both when you talking to the Lord you
praying to him when you in the
congregation and you praying you are
praying I hope that helps sister I
really do and that is asking God for
petition or giving him thanks yes
sir all right thank you for that hope
that answer that question as we move on
to our next yes we are now teritory
right that is correct we are now into
tonight's Q&A for Wednesday January the
8th
2025 me too for you Jones ask if a uh
ask when did the current Gentiles Jews
which they're not appear in the Bible or
did it just start in
1948 wa before that guess
caller first thing is the Jew the one
that call them Jew is not a gentile
let's see what a gentile is go to
Genesis the 10th chapter read verses
1-5 Genesis 10 verses 1-5 says now these
are the generations of the sons of Noah
shim ham and japheth and unto them were
Sons born After the flood the sons of
japheth gmer and Magog and midi and
Javan and tubal and meach and Tyrus and
the sons of gomar ashes and RAB and
togar and the sons of Jaan Elisha and
Alisha and Tarsus and kidum and do
dodanim by these were the aisles of the
Gentiles divided in their lands everyone
after his tongue after their families in
their
Nations so now the Gentiles are the
children of japat which we call regular
white folks but you got Jews people
that's running around call themselves
Jews they they White too but they are
not gentille let me show you where the G
where the Jew came from uh because the
Jew the one that called himself Jew he
the son of Esau or an
Edomite go into Genesis 25th
chapter read verses 20 to
21 then we going to
skip okay Genesis 25 veres 20 to 21 says
and Isaac was 40 years old
when he took Rebecca the wife the
daughter of Bethel the S Syrian of
padanaram the sister of laan and Syrian
and Isaac
in Isaac is the son of
Abraham Abraham come out
of out of uh uhuh
sham he didn't come out of
jai just want you to let you know
that he can't be a gentile and neither
can his children but keep ring what
verse verse 21 and Isaac entreated the
Lord for his wife because she was Barren
and the Lord was entreated of him and
Rebecca his wife
conceived now skip down to verse 24 and
read 24 through 26 okay and when her
days to be delivered were fulfilled
behold there were twins in her womb and
the first came came out red all over
like an hairy garment and they called
his name Esau and after that came his
brother out and his hand took hold on
Esau's Hill and his name was called
Jacob and Isaac was three score years
old when she be
them so the one that calls himself a Jew
is not a gentile he's a Hebrew just like
we are he just not an Israelite even
though he white but people trying to say
well you know how can you get the white
and black come out of the same person
look everybody on this planet came out
of Adam and Eve didn't they right so the
whole thing is so they are not Gentiles
they are Hebrews and what happened here
with the rest of the question is is that
uh uh uh God gave them the land of Mount
SE then they was driven out of the land
by the nepetin which is Arabs and they
was driven into Southern
Jerusalem and what happened was uh uh uh
and and they was in southern Jerusalem
and that's the time of the hism monian
which are called
mes they which are
Israelites mostly out of the tribe of
Judah and Benjamin but anyway they was
fighting against the syrians and for a
minute there they took over took your
land back CU they had been driven out of
the land
and in the southern
Jerusalem was was full of Edomite
because the netin drove them down in
southern Jerusalem which is called the
Neal so when the mes took over they
forced the which are called
Jews to convert to
Judaism and that was about that was in
the uh in the BC and I say around and uh
uh uh and I say
around that was around
34 or 126 rather BC so when they
converted
them they started call themselves Jews
by religion so now around 70
AD the Titus the Roman general Titus
destroyed Jerusalem down to the ground
and took all of the Israelites the Jews
and Scattered them all over the
Mediterranean and so when he scattered
Israel over then what happened was Edom
just start calling thems by the name of
the land which was Jew they started call
themselves Jews so they was no longer
called or Adomian and that's
why this thing come up in Revelation go
to Revelation
2:9 and read 29 and 39 read
it okay revelation
says I Know Thy works and tribulation
and poverty but Thou Art rich I know the
blasphemy of them which say they are
Jews and are not but are the synagogue
of
Satan verse
39 verse 39 says behold I will make them
of the synagogue of Satan which say they
are Jews and are not but do lie behold I
will make them to come and worship
before thy feet and to know that I have
loved
thee so now in 7 ad when Jerusalem when
the original Jews was scattered out of
the
land Esau was already in southern
Jerusalem found the knab he just moved
in and assumed the name Jew tell you
this in over go to over now and read
verses 1 and two and Skip down to verse
10 and read to
14 Joel Amos and Obadiah oh
yeah Obadiah and what verse to start off
with sir one and
two the vision of Obadiah thus sayeth
the Lord God concerning Edom we have
heard a rumor from the Lord and an
ambassador is sent among the the Heathen
arise ye and let us rise up against her
in battle behold I have made thee small
among the Heathen Thou Art greatly
despised so now this is talk about about
the one that called himself a Jew they
they dislike him almost more than they
dislike us now skip down to verse 10 and
continue for thy violence against thy
brother Jacob shall cover thee and thou
shalt be cut off
forever uhhuh in the day in the day that
thou stood on the other side in the day
that the strangers carried away captive
his forces and foreigners entered into
his Gates and cast lots upon Jerusalem
even thou was as one of
them when the Romans went and all when
when uh took them out then people
started to go in there ARS among them
start to lay claim to Israel to J
judah's land he said you was among them
that went and then was doing that go
ahead and read but thou should us not
have looked on the day of thy brother in
the day that he became a stranger
neither should thou have rejoiced over
the children of Judah in the day of
their destruction neither should thou
have spoken proudly in the day of
distress thou should us not oh go Ahad
thou should us not have entered into the
gate of my people in the day of their
Calamity yay thou should as not have
looked on their Affliction in the day of
their Calamity nor have laid hands on
their substance in the day of their
Calamity do now Esau went in our gates
they took part our land then they took
our sub which our culture our pictures
everything that belong to us they took
it and they're going to be
there until the Lord come skip now and
read uh
uh read uh uh let's
see uh verse
21 so when the Lord come go Zion is in
Jerusalem let's see who the Lord's going
to find now go ahead and saviors shall
come up on Mount Zion to judge the Mount
of Esau and the kingdom shall be the
Lords when the Lord come and said savior
that's after the first resurrection that
mean it' be more than one Jesus if Jesus
and all the people in the first
resurrection when they go up on Mount
Zion they going to find Esau there even
though he called he called himself by
our name but Esau Israel was driven out
in 7 ad Esau went in but then in 135 ad
the Romans
scattered the out of there the
so-called Jew out of there and from one
uh uh uh from 135
ad they
was out of the land too but then in
1948 they brought him back because they
were the only one that had the name
Jew because we called
everything but not Jew so they was so
they was driven out 135 ad and then the
Gentiles got together in 140 in 1948 and
put them back in the land they've been
there ever
since all have to say all right hope
that answers your question as we move on
to our next one next question time out
Houston asks was Jesus crucified at the
third hour ma uh Mark 15 verse 25 or
still on trial after the sixth hour John
19 vers
14-6 brother
Jerome no he wasn't still on trial uh
during the six hour but let's go read
those um verses that you gave Mark 15
and 25
it says and it was the third hour and
they crucified him now let's go to uh St
John 19 read 14-
16 it says and it was the preparation of
the Passover in about the sixth hour and
he saith unto the Jews behold your king
but they cried out away with him away
with him crucify him pilate saith unto
them shall I crucify your king the chief
priest answered we have no King but
Caesar then delivered he him therefore
unto them to be crucified and they took
Jesus and led him
away okay to put this in chronological
order when you read verse
14 verse 14 is when he was already on
the cross
but but in actuality verse 15 and 16 was
before he was on the cross okay that was
before the third hour when they put him
on the cross okay so now go back to that
um
Mark okay
15 okay and let's pick it up at verse 14
and that verse 14 read 14
through 20 okay and that'll that'll
cover the verse 15 and 16 in St John 19
okay events that happened before the
third hour okay go ahead and read it
then pilate said unto them why what evil
hath he done and they cried out the more
exceedingly crucify him and so pilate
willing to con willing to content the
people
released Barnabas or barabus unto them
and delivered Jesus when he had scourged
him to be
crucified and the soldiers led him away
into the Hall calling called PR
pratorum and they called together the
whole band and they clothed him with
purple and platted a crown of thorns and
put it about his head and began to
salute him hell King of the Jews
and they smote him on the head with a
reed and did spit upon him and bowing
and bowing their knees worshiped him and
when they had mocked him they took off
the purple from him and put his own
clothes on him and led him out to
crucify him okay so now those are events
that happened before the third hour when
they put him on the cross so now that
verse that you gave in your question
skip down to verse 25 that's the third
hour and it was the third hour and they
crucified and they crucified him so then
when you go to the back to the St
John Chapter
19 Verse
14 that was after he was already on the
cross in the sixth hour okay he just
they just happen to put verse 15 and 16
dealing with events that was before the
third hour okay and he was on the cross
from the third hour through the sixth
hour through the ninth hour until and he
stayed on the cross till he
died that's all I got
on horable death indeed
brother all right thank you for that
hope that answered their question as we
move on to our next one moving on ah
says I have a family member who chooses
not to work and benefits from
governmental assistance but constantly
ask me for money or to order food I'm
conflicted because I give to those less
fortunate but I also feel like if I
continually give to him I'm rewarding
laziness because he is an able-body man
and Genesis 3: 19 is given so
AHS how should I handle
this how should that be handled brother
Julius you're muted
Julius my apologies first of all um you
you have to stop being inable if this
person is able-bodied there's nothing
physically or mentally wrong with them
and they just lazy or with a book called
aul and they don't want to work let's
look at what the book
say Genesis 3:19 let's read her verse
she
gave in the sweat of thy face shalt thou
eat bread till thou return unto the
ground for out of it was thou taken for
dust Thou Art and to dust shalt thou
return so the Lord set the pre
precedence in the beginning you going to
work for a
living got to work for a living let's go
to 2
Thessalonians chapter 3 2 Thessalonians
chapter
3 there's no because if if if if uh uh
he refused to work that means somebody
else is getting
robbed second Thessalonians chapter 3
pick this up at verse 12 2 Thessalonians
three and pick this up at verse 7 I'm
sorry verse 7 go ahead and read it for
yourselves know how ye ought to follow
us for we behave not ourselves
disorderly among you neither did we eat
any man's bread for not for nothing go
ahead but rought with labor and travail
night and day that we might not be
chargeable to any of you Paul said we
work night and day so we wouldn't be
dependent upon
you go ahead and read not because we
have not power but to make ourselves an
end sample unto you to follow us in
other words you got to work for a living
you got to work for a living skip all
the way down uh uh verse uh well you
could re read verse uh wow verse 11 go
ahead for we hear that there are some
I'm sorry I'm sorry James continue at
verse 10 to uh okay to 11 go ahead for
even when we were with you this week
commanded you that if any would not work
neither should he eat
man if a person don't work they
shouldn't
eat Ain't Nothing free go ahead at verse
11 that'll be it for we hear that there
are some which walk among you disorderly
working not at all but are busy bodies
so the Bible said if a man don't work he
shouldn't eat
so sister although you have a soft and a
a soft heart and a giving spirit you Mak
a person dependent upon you if a man
don't work he shouldn't eat he's
able-bodied he could do
something he could sweep floors he could
whatever it is he got to make his own
living that's all like that on that
Corel you're you're muted brother
my apologies too thank you for that hope
that answered their question as we move
on moving on ah also asks is it okay to
listen to songs that makes you feel sad
or makes you sad or should I thrive to
be marry in the heart in
heart well that's your choice if you
want to listen to songs that that make
you
sad um but also you should Thrive to be
merry and heart so you go listen to them
sad songs and when you get through play
that song that say Don't Worry Be
Happy let's go to Proverbs the 15th
chapter Proverbs
okay and let's uh let's read one verse
let's read that verse uh 13
there Proverbs
15 and verse 13
go ahead brother a merry heart maketh a
cheerful countenance but by sorrow of
the heart the spirit is broken so you
have to be careful when you dealing with
some things that can break your spirit
and make you sad and fill all down but a
merry heart it maketh a cheerful
countenance now turn over to Proverbs 17
right quick Proverbs 17 okay and let's
pick it up and let's read read that
verse
22 go ahead a a merry heart doeth good
like a medicine but a broken Spirit dth
the bones sometimes feeling sad and down
can sometimes give you that old broken
Spirit dry your bones but a merry heart
is like medicine so these are the things
and especially if you f the true and
living God that is a reason to be very
happy isn't it brother James yes sir and
turn back to Psalms 95 and pick it up
read 1 through3 and that'll be it Psalms
95: 1-3 says oh come let us sing unto
the Lord let us Make a Joyful Noise to
the rock of our Salvation than to our
God go ahead let us come before his
presence with Thanksgiving and Make a
Joyful Noise unto him with Psalms for
the Lord is a great God and a great king
Above All Gods all right so those are
some scriptures to let you know that you
should be seeking that happiness in that
joyful heart that is like a medicine
because sometimes sad songs can take you
somewhere that um you don't need to be
but it's your choice but you should be
striving after that Merry heart because
you got a reason to be thankful that's
all I
got all right we're go moving on to the
next question
question uh Tracy bures asks what does
Quicken
mean what does Quicken mean quicking can
be you know it can change you for the
good or for the better it can change you
from flesh to Spirit from dead to alive
so let's uh pick it up in Psalms 119
right quick Psalms
119 what does Quicken
mean okays 119 go through some skipping
brother pick it up at that verse 33 for
me go ahead okay 33 says teach me oh
Lord the way of thy statutes and I shall
keep it until the end uhhuh give me
understanding and I shall keep thy law
yay I shall observe it with my whole
heart go ahead make me to go in the path
of thy Commandments for therein do I
Delight so these Commandments and this
teach me oh Lord and when you learn what
thus says the Lord it can Quicken you
make you alive change your ways go
ahead incline my heart unto thine
testimonies and not to
covetousness right turn away mine eyes
from beholding vanity and Quicken thou
me in thy way yes turn away mine eyes
from beholding vanity nothing and
Quicken me in thy way make me recognize
the things that are good things that are
right and the things that please you
read verse 40 and we go to skip again go
ahead behold I have longed after thy
precepts Quicken me in thy righteousness
that's why the Lord said when you search
for him with all your heart he'll
Quicken you verse 88 skip down to 88 for
me and go ahead Quicken me after thy
loving kindness so shall I keep the
testimony of thy mouth
yeah fix me Lord so I can keep all the
testimonies of your mouth 149 go
ahead 149
says hear my voice according unto thy
loving kindness oh Lord Quicken me
according to thy judgment and read
154 plead my cause and Deliver Me
Quicken me according to Thy word because
when the Lord Quicken you with this word
it would change you and have you to walk
in the ways that please him now let's go
last place Romans 8 Romans 8 and read
about another quickening here Romans 8
and when you get there Brothers pick it
up at that verse 10 okay Romans 8 and
10 here's another
quick and if Christ be in you the body
is dead because of sin but the spirit is
life because of righteousness yes
because you've been quickened from them
dead ways and the things that upset God
go ahead but if the spirit of him that
raised up Jesus from the dead dwell in
you he that raised up Christ from the
dead shall also Quicken your mortal
bodies by his spirit that dwelleth in
you uhhuh therefore brethren we are deor
not to the flesh to live after the flesh
for if we for if ye live after the flesh
ye shall die but if ye through the
spirit do mortify the Deeds of the body
ye shall live yeah so Quicken can you
know like I said it can change for good
or it can change from flesh to Spirit or
it can even raise the dead and Quicken
them and make them alive so that's my
explanation for that and that's all I
got we hope
go right also also said that Jesus was
put to death in the flesh but it was
quickened in the spirit other words he
was but then he and then he was made
alive that mean he rose from the dead
Qui merely
means he rose from the dead whether it's
spiritual or whether it's
physical all I have to say all right
hope that answered your question sister
Deborah time check as we move move on to
our next one yes time is
8:55 daughter of Judah asked were Adam
and Eve created on the sixth day or per
Genesis 2:
5-7 after God rested on the seventh day
is that the Eighth Day Theory brother
Julius no that's not the Eighth Day
Theory has nothing to do with the Eighth
Day
uh let's go to Genesis and the answer is
yes Adam and Eve was made on the sixth
day let's go to Genesis
1 Genesis 1 and pick it up at verse
26 it says and God said let us make man
in our image after our likeness and let
them have dominion over the fish of the
sea and over the fowl of the air and
over the cattle and over all the Earth
and over every creeping thing that
creepeth upon the Earth uhhuh so God
created man in his own image in the
image of God created he him male and
female created he them male and female
created he them go to Genesis chapter 5
last
place Genesis 5 and read verse 1 and two
this is the book of the generations of
Adam in the day that God created man in
the likeness of God made he him male and
female created he them and blessed them
and called their name Adam in the day
when they were created and I I apologize
I should have read Genesis 1 and verse
31 the book says and the evening and the
morning were the sixth day so yes the
answer Adam and Eve was
created on the same day she was just
inside the man that's
all all right hope that answers your
question as we move on to our
next all right uh next question is from
philosophy philosophy says are we
allowed to celebrate the other holidays
besides Easter and Christmas or is
Valentine's Day and New Year's
considered pagan
all right guest
caller Valentine is Pagan it come from
St
Valentine as far as New Year's concerned
celebrate the new God's New Year start
in the month Abel which uh switches
between the last of March and the 1st of
April but as far as this manmade New
Years we can't call it Pagan because
it's not saying that you praising some
God
so the Bible don't say nothing uh uh say
that you can or
cannot so I can't give you an answer
whether you celebrate it or not just let
you know that is not God's New Year
that's all I have to say all right hope
that answers your question next question
June green asks if a husband and wife
are alive at the time of Jesus return
and also meet the Lord in the air to
then eventually come back down to Earth
are they still husband and wife as they
had no need of the
Resurrection brother
Jerome
um well they going to become Spirit
beings uh at the resurrection uh um and
but the the marriage won't be no issue
once they come up in that first
resurrection
you know so let's let's go take look at
Luke see what the Lord say about it Luke
Chapter
20 okay and pick it up at verse 29 read
it to uh
um read it to uh
36 okay Luke 20 and verse 29 says there
were therefore seven Brethren and the
first took a wife and died without
children and the second took her a wife
and he died childless and the third took
her in like manner the seven also and
they left no children and died last of
all the woman the woman died also
therefore in the re in the resurrection
whose wife of them is she for seven had
heard a wife and Jesus answering said
unto them the children children of this
world marri and are given in marriage
but they which shall be accounted worthy
to obtain that world and the
resurrection from the dead neither marry
nor are given in marriage neither can
they die anymore for they are equal unto
the angels and are the children of God
being the children of the
Resurrection yeah so according to your
question it says also meet the Lord in
the air if they meet the Lord in the air
they make in the first resurrection if
they in the first resurrection that
issue about them being married when they
was in the flesh that won't be no issue
you know they're going to be they going
to be God actually you know so that's
all I got on that all right thank you
for that and let's uh go to this next
question here and see why time all right
the time is 9:01 I bro
last question okay last
question um read the
Bible uh says can you please explain
first John 5 verse 16 what is sin not
unto death I assume this is speaking
about Sin in ignorance versus sinning
willfully all right brother what you say
for our last question of the evening
yeah let's go to that uh 1 John 5 and16
and read that brother James
okay if any man see his brother sin a
sin which is not unto death he shall ask
and he shall give him life for them that
sin not unto death there is a sin unto
death I do not say that he shall shall
pray for it so let's let's eliminate
what the sin onto death is let's go to
uh Matthew 12 and read verses 31 and
32 Matthew 31 and
32 Matthew 12 verses 31 and 32 says
wherefore I say unto you all manner of
sin and blasphemy shall be given unto
shall be forgiven unto to men but the
blasphemy against the Holy Ghost shall
not be forgiven unto men and whosoever
speaketh the word against the son of man
it shall be forgiven him but whosoever
speaketh against the Holy Ghost it shall
not be forgiven him neither in this
world nor e neither in the world to come
so that sin we reading here will not be
forgiven but in terms of sinning and
ignorance which you mentioned which is
uh written in in uh
Leviticus 4 1-3 and also in numbers 15
ver 22 to 30 you can read them on you on
your own it also talks about in Hebrews
10 26 about willfully s judgment coming
with that also in Hebrews
6 about taste partaking of the Holy
Ghost and sinning and the Judgment that
comes with that
so what we are not to do is to sin
willfully against the Holy Ghost you got
ananas and
Safari they
sin by doing what they did and Peter ask
him why did you do do this against the
Holy Ghost and they
died so what we are to do is just abide
in the word of God and we don't have to
worry about all that I would say do
that yes sir that's correct and if you
blaspheme against the Holy Ghost you do
not work for God because you know the
truth and you're telling the LIE yes sir
all right we thank you for that brother
hope that answered that question sister
Deborah time Check Yes the time is
905 oh all right well we have ran out of
time and we also recognize that you have
sent some questions in that we did not
have time to answer but don't resubmit
that question because we'll take it and
we will deal with that question next
week so until we all come together again
we want to thank you all for viewing we
ask you to be
safe be blessed
stay prayed up may the Lord have mercy
on us all as brother James closes us
out Our Father which art in heaven
Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom come
thy will be done in earth as it is in
heaven give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us our debts as we forgive
our debors and lead us not into
temptation but deliver Us from Evil for
thine is the kingdom and the power and
the glory forever in Jesus name we pray
amen